<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Parmis Mohaghegh</title>
    <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Parmis Mohaghegh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mparmis.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op: Thoughtexchange</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/te/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/te/</guid>
      <description>Overview
I joined a software company called Thoughtexchange for my second Co-op semester. Thoughtexchange has a mission to help leaders &amp;ldquo;hear from the unheard majority, not just the loudest voices&amp;rdquo;.
Thoughtexchange provides software and professional services to enable customers to lead productive group conversations with 10 to 10,000 people, ask an open-ended question, and encourage participants to give input and read and rate others&amp;rsquo; thoughts. Then their AI and machine learning identifies the interest groups and finds the common ground between them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBC Autonomous Driving Competition</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/353/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/353/</guid>
      <description>Overview:
I was one of the lucky students to be able to take ENPH 353, a Machine Learning Competition Course that was offered for the very first time at UBC.
The first half of the course consisted of individual projects to practice some of the most recent techniques and developments in control software and data classification. For the second half, we formed teams of two and had 6 weeks to get our simulated robot ready for the competition day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue-Avengers Competition</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/robot/</guid>
      <description>Overview
This post is about my favorite project! The fully autonomous robot that my team and I developed over the summer of 2019!
The famous Engineering Physics Autonomous Robot Competition has been running for 20 years over the summers. This is a hands-on project course in which teams of 4 work together to build an autonomous robot from scratch. And when I say scratch, I mean scratch!
Over the summer, our team spent roughly three months brainstorming, designing, prototyping, and testing to bring our robot to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op: UBC Robotics and Control Lab</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/rcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/rcl/</guid>
      <description>Overview
I worked at UBC Robotics and Control Lab (RCL) during my first Co-op semester from January to April 2019. RCL carries out research in medical image analysis, image-guided diagnosis and interventions, telerobotic and robotic control of mobile machines and manipulators. Applications range from the integration of real-time imaging in image-guided therapy, and new concepts for the control of large hydraulic mobile machines such as excavators to small medical telerobotic micromanipulators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cmd-f 2020: Vancouver&#39;s All-female Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cmf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cmf/</guid>
      <description>Overview
Cmd-f is western Canada’s first all-female Hackathon. This year, It took place over 24 hours from March 7th to March 8th.
This Hackathon had several categories we could work on and my team and I decided to work on prototyping a mobile app that addressed two of these categories: Community Connector and Empowering Women Through Technology, and that&amp;rsquo;s when we came up with the idea of HealthBud.
HealthBud is an app that is focused on making physical activity more accessible and enjoyable for women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPEN 221</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen221/</guid>
      <description>Overview The most challenging software architecture course at UBC!
Page in Progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPEN312</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen312/</guid>
      <description>Overview Going back to the basics. 8051 assembly projects!
Page in Progress</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>