<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Parmis Mohaghegh</title>
    <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Parmis Mohaghegh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mparmis.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op: Thoughtexchange</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/te/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/te/</guid>
      <description>Overview:
I joined a software company called Thoughtexchange for my second Co-op semester. Thoughtexchange has a mission to help leaders &amp;ldquo;hear from the unheard majority, not just the loudest voices&amp;rdquo;. Not only did I get a chance to work on a very interesting project and acquire a variety of new technical skills, but I also realized how working at a company that values providing equal opportunity and has created a wonderful culture of collaboration can make my work more enjoyable and purposeful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBC Autonomous Driving Competition</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/353/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/353/</guid>
      <description>Overview:
I was one of the lucky students to be able to take ENPH 353, a Machine Learning Competition Course that was offered for the very first time at UBC.
The first half of the course consisted of individual projects to practice some of the most recent techniques and developments in control software and data classification. For the second half, we formed teams of two and had 6 weeks to get our simulated robot ready for the competition day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue-Avengers Competition</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/robot/</guid>
      <description>Overview:
This post is about my favourite project! The fully autonomous robot that my team and I developed over the summer of 2019!
The famous Engineering Physics Autonomous Robot Competition has been running for 20 years over the summers. This is a hands on project course in which teams of four work together to build an autonomous robot from scratch. And when I say scratch, I mean scratch!
Over the summer, our team spent roughly three months brainstorming, designing, prototyping, and testing to bring our robot to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cmd-f 2020: Vancouver&#39;s All-female* Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cmf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cmf/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-op: UBC Robotics and Control Lab</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/rcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/rcl/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPEN 221</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen221/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPEN312</title>
      <link>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mparmis.github.io/post/cpen312/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>